어허, 얘들이 정말
None of that.
Not while you're under my roof!
내 지붕 아래선 용납 못해
뭐?
Just because I know about you
doesn't mean I like looking at it.
내가 너희 둘을 잘 안다고
그 꼴도 보기 좋은 줄 알아?
오디션에 간다고 하지 않았나?
Aren't you supposed to be
at an audition?
내가 중년의 흑인 여자가
아니라서 미안하다
I'm sorry I'm not
a middle-aged black woman.
또 가끔 엉뚱한 오디션에
나가는 것도 송구스럽고
I'm also sorry if sometimes
I go to the wrong audition.
이것들 봐
내가 너희 관계를 모르는 척하면
너희도 평상시처럼 행동해야지
If I pretend to not know about you...
...then you pretend
there's nothing to know.
- 알았어
- 미안해
미안
Sorry.
I can hear that!
다 들린다
레이첼 출근했어
Rachel's at work.
그래도 들려
I can still hear you!
The One With the Yeti
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
What's that?
왔구나, 그건 뭐야?
My mom sent me an heirloom
that belonged to my grandmother.
엄마가 가보를 보내왔는데
할머니가 갖고 계시던 거래
Can you believe it?
믿어지니?
A year ago I had no family,
and now I have heirlooms!
1년 전엔 가족도 없던 내게
가보가 생기다니, 미치겠다
The only heirloom I ever got
was a feather boa.
내 유일한 가보는 털목도리였어
Got if from my dad.
He got it from his dad.
아버지한테 받았지
원래 할아버지 건데
How did I ever get born?
내가 어떻게 태어났지?
Oh, God!
엄마야!
Soft.
부드러운데?
Is this mink?
밍크인가?
그래, 왜 엄마가
모피를 보냈을까
Why would my mother send me a fur?
Doesn't she know me but at all?
날 몰라도 이렇게 몰라?
내게도 멋진 코트가 있지만
동물을 죽여서 만든 건 아냐
I have a fine coat that no innocent
animals suffered to make.
Just Filipino kids who worked
their fingers bloody...
9살짜리 필리핀 애들이
손가락 피나게 만든 거지
시간 당 12센트 받고
...for 12 cents an hour.
I made that up.
내가 지어낸 얘기야
얘들아
이봐, 로스
You can't put up flyers in here.
여기 전단 붙이면 안 돼
How come?
Everybody else does.
왜요, 다들 하는데
You can't.
자넨 안 돼
뭔데 그래?
What is that?
- 어디 봐
- 물건 몇 개 처분하려고
I'm getting rid of some things.
오빠 물건 전부잖아
This is all of your things.
그래, 맞아
Yes, it is.
괜찮아
에밀리가 새 걸 원하니까
It's good. Emily thinks
we should get all new stuff.
우리 둘만의 물건
따끈따끈한 새 거
Stuff that's just ours.
Together. Brand new.
레이첼 손길이 닿은 건
모두 팔겠다는 뜻이네
So it's a get-rid-of-anything-
Rachel-ever-touched sale.
Touched, used, sat on, slept on....
만지고 쓰고
앉고 잤던 거지
I'll take it all.
내가 다 살게
로스, 정말 괜찮겠어?
You're okay with that?
If I can just do what Emily wants...
에밀리만 뉴욕으로 온다면
내가 지금 뭔들 못하겠어
...and get her to New York,
it will be fine.
좀 심한 것 같지 않아?
Isn't that a little extreme?
After what I did, can you blame her?
내가 한 짓이 있는데
에밀리를 탓할 순 없지
말도 마, 그 정도는 약과야
You got off easy.
내 친구 실비는 침대에서
남편이 딴 여자 이름 말했다고
When my friend's husband said
another name in bed...
저주를 내려 거시기를
파랗게 만들었대
...she cursed him
and turned his thingy green.
I guess I'm lucky Emily is not magic.
에밀리는 마녀가
아니라서 다행이다
Oh, she is.
맞을 거야
We all are.
우린 다 마녀지
What is he doing?
이게 무슨 짓이지?
Emily thinks Ross' furniture
has got Rachel cooties?
에밀리는 로스의 가구에
레이첼 벌레라도 있단 거야?
- 흥분하지 마
- 아니, 모든 게 엉망이야
Calm down, Joey.
Everything's getting all messed up!
Emily won't let Ross see Rachel.
로스는 레이첼을 못 보지만
우린 레이첼을 계속 볼 거지?
We won't stop seeing Rachel.
Hence, Ross stops seeing us.
향후 로스는 우리까지 못 봐
I hate this.
Everything's changing.
정말 싫다
모든 게 변하고 있어
그래, 로스는 떠나가고
조이는 '향후'라고 하고
We're losing Ross.
Joey said "hence."
나도 즐거운 건 아니지만
오빠가 행복하다니까...
I'm not happy about this either,
but if Ross says he's happy...
에밀리에 대한 감정은
묻어두는 게 좋겠어
...then we have to keep
our feelings to ourselves.
Are you cool with that?
너도 동의하지?
아니
하지만 알다시피 난 배우야
But, you know, I'm an actor.
I'll act cool.
연기로 커버할게
Probably be some of the hardest acting
I've ever done.
가장 힘든 연기가
될지도 모르겠다
Maybe I'll play it with a mustache.
콧수염을 달면 어떨까?
난 여기 오면
오싹 소름이 끼쳐
Storage rooms give me the creeps.
Please hurry up, honey.
모니카, 부탁이야
빨리 끝내 줘
동그란 와플을 먹고 싶으면
동그란 와플 틀을 찾아야지
If you want little round waffles,
wait till I find the iron.
I want the little round waffles.
- 동그란 와플 먹고 싶어
- 좋아
Here it is!
여기 있다
바퀴 잡는 연막탄 바로 밑에
Right underneath the can of bug bomb.
Is the best place to put something
that cooks food underneath poison?
요리도구를 독약 밑에서
찾으니까 기분이 묘하네
You know what?
I'll have toast.
됐어, 난 그냥 토스트 먹을래
엄마야!
터뜨려! 어서!
Fog him! Fog him!
터뜨려!
I don't know what to do
about this coat.
이 코트 어떡하지?
I'll take it.
내가 가질게
That might work.
그래도 좋고
What do you think?
좋다, 어때?
You're on in five, Ms. Minnelli.
5분 후에 공연입니다
미넬리 양
No, it's just a bit sudden.
아니, 약간 뜻밖이라서
It's great, okay?
I am totally onboard.
물론 좋지
내가 왜 싫겠어
I love you too.
All right, bye.
나도 사랑해, 안녕
What's the matter?
왜 그래?
아무 것도, 사실은...
멋진 소식이야
Nothing. No, actually...
...great news!
방금 에밀리랑 통화했는데
새 아파트로 이사 가야겠다
I just spoke with Emily...
...and looks like I'm moving
to a new apartment.
얏호!
Why?
왜?
에밀리 생각에
내가 동의했거든
Her thought is, and I agree...
...fresh new furniture,
why not a fresh new apartment?
새 가구를 장만하는데
새 아파트는 왜 안 되겠어?
에밀리 사촌이
세로 주는 건데
Her cousin has a place to sublet.
한쪽으로는 강이 보이고
다른 쪽엔 컬럼비아가 보여
It's got a view
of the river and Columbia.
That's way uptown!
That's three trains away...
전철을 세 번이나 갈아타야
하잖아, 진짜 좋겠다
...which is great!
I love to ride that rail.
나도 정말 타고 싶거든
You're okay with this?
너 진짜 괜찮은 거야?
그래, 직장에서 좀 멀지만
It's kind of far from work...
...but I'll get so much done
on the commute.
통근 시간을 잘 활용하면 돼
I've been given the gift of time.
시간을 선물 받은 거지
That's so funny. Last Christmas
I got the gift of space.
그거 재밌다, 지난 성탄절에
난 공간을 선물 받았는데
We should get them together
and make a continuum.
그 둘을 합쳐서
시공연속체를 만들자
Now he's moving?
이사까지 가?
Man, what is Emily doing to him?
젠장, 에밀리가 대체
무슨 짓을 한 거지?
아야!
He's not even here!
지금 로스 없잖아
You guys!
얘들아, 들어봐
We were in the storage area,
and we saw this creepy man.
방금 창고에 들어갔다
진짜 무서운 사람을 봤어
미치광이 같은 눈에
털이 덥수룩한 게 꼭...
It was this crazy-eyed,
hairy beast-man.
It was like a Big Foot
or a yeti or something.
빅풋이나 설인 같았다니까
도끼를 들고 덤벼들어서
레이첼이 연막탄을 터뜨렸어
He came at us,
so Rachel used a bug bomb on him.
I pulled the tab
and I just fogged his yeti ass.
그래, 뚜껑을 벗겨서
엉덩이에 쑤셔 넣었지
Like, dark hair, bushy beard?
- 검은색 머리에 덥수룩한 수염?
- 그래
Yeah, you fogged Danny.
대니를 엿 먹였군
Please! We did not fog Danny.
대니를 엿 먹이긴!
대니가 누군데?
Who's Danny?
Danny just moved in.
아래층에 이사 왔어
넉 달 간 안데스를 탐험했대
He just got back from a four-month
trek in the Andes. Nice fella.
좋은 친구지
He's nice.
You know, you always...
그래, 좋기도 하겠다
넌 늘 우리가 엿 먹이는
사람들만 편드냐?
...stick up for the people we fog.
- 네
- 안녕하세요?
You might not remember us,
but we're the girls that fogged you.
모르시겠지만 저희가
연막탄을 터뜨렸어요
- 정말 죄송하게 됐네요
- 네
We're really sorry we fogged you.
알았어요
저기, 잘 아시겠지만
그럴 뜻은 없었답니다
Just so you know,
we didn't mean to fog you.
We thought you were
like a yeti or something.
우린 설인인 줄 알았거든요
알았어요
네?
안녕하세요
Sorry to bother you, but we can't
accept your acceptance of our apology.
자꾸 방해해서 죄송한데
건성으로 대답하지 말고
It doesn't really seem
like you mean it.
- 사과를 받아주셨으면 해요
- 그래요
알았어요
That guy is so rude!
정말 무례한 사람이네
Really!
What is with that guy?
진짜, 어떻게 생겨먹었기에
You'd forgive me if I fogged you.
너라면 용서해줄 거잖아
You did, a little bit.
나도 연기 좀 먹었어
Oh, my God, honey.
I'm so sorry.
세상에, 정말 미안하다
-I totally forgive you.
-Really?
- 깨끗이 용서할게
- 진짜?
- 나야
- 그래
You know my friend Chris
who owns the crematorium?
저기, 화장터 운영하는
내 친구 크리스 알지?
Crematorium Chris? Sure.
화장터 크리스? 그럼
He said he would cremate
my fur coat for free...
걔가 내 코트를
화장해준대, 공짜로
...if I bring in the next person
I know who dies.
죽은 사람 하나
소개시켜주면
Oh, my God!
세상에
Oh, my God.
Look at these pelts!
이 모피 좀 봐...
Don't get too attached.
She's having it cremated.
너무 좋아하지 마
불태울 거래
뭐?
피비?
자기야?
You're quirky, and I get a big kick
out of it. We all do.
너 별난 거 난 아주 좋아
사실 우리 모두 그렇지만...
But if you destroy
a coat like this...
이런 코트를 망치는 건
자연에 대한 범죄야
...that is like a crime
against nature.
Not nature. Fashion!
자연이 아니라 패션!
This is fashion?
- 이게 패션이야?
- 그래
So to you, death is fashion?
너한테는 죽음도 패션이니?
그거 재미있다
That's funny.
Here's Phoebe...
지금부터 피비가 털 많은
짐승의 가죽을 선보입니다
...sporting cutting-edge
hairy carcass...
...from, you know, the steel traps
of wintry Russia.
동토의 땅 러시아에서
철제 덫으로 잡았다네요
이게 정말 좋아 보여?
You really think this looks good?
Because I do!
진짜 좋네
I miss you too.
I can't wait to see you.
그래, 나도 자기가
빨리 보고 싶어
I love you. Bye.
사랑해, 안녕
What is in here, rocks?
이게 뭐지? 바위?
아니, 화석 샘플 콜렉션이야
No, it's my collection
of fossil samples.
So, rocks.
그럼 바위네
I'll miss this apartment.
이 아파트가 그리울 거야
You know, Ben took his first steps
right over there.
벤이 저기서 걸음마를 뗐어
Remember when I ran into this
and it knocked me out?
내가 여기 부딪혀서
실신할 뻔도 했었지?
I love this place.
난 여기가 좋아
To tell the truth,
I wish I didn't have to move.
사실 이사 가긴 싫은데
그렇게 좋은 것만은
아니라는 뜻이야?
Are you saying that you're not
entirely happy about this?
If Emily gave me a choice
에밀리가 내게
선택의 기회를 준다면...
You do have a choice!
선택의 기회는 있어
왜 에밀리 말만 들어
지금 제정신이야?
Why are you listening to her?
Are you crazy?
왜?
에밀리가 원하는 건 옳지 않아
이건 완전히... 아야!
It's not right what Emily wants
you to do. She's totally
Stop pinching me!
그만 좀 꼬집어
로스의 행복을 위해서
조용히 있으라고 했지?
You guys said to keep my mouth shut
if Ross was happy, right?
He just told me
that he's not entirely happy.
근데 얘가 지금 꼭
행복한 것만은 아니래
What's going on?
무슨 일이지?
We all hate Emily!
우린 에밀리 싫어
아냐
No, Ross, we do not hate Emily.
에밀리가 싫은 건 아냐
We just think that
you're having to sacrifice...
단지 에밀리의 행복을 위해서
오빠가 치르는 희생이 너무 커
...a whole lot to make her happy.
그거야
지금 에밀리의 행동은
약간 이치에 닿지 않아
We just think that maybe
she's being a little unreasonable.
그래, 이치에 안 닿아
Yes, unreasonable.
Unreasonable?
이치에 안 닿아?
How about we have this conversation
when one of you marries?
너희 중 하나가 결혼할 때
이런 대화를 해볼까?
You have no idea what it takes
to make a marriage work.
결혼에 따르는 희생이
어떤 건지 알기나 해?
그건 협상이고 언제나
내 맘에 드는 것도 아냐
It's compromise.
Do you always like it? No.
Do you do it? Yes.
하지만 해야 할 때가 있지
늘 웃음과 행복, 달콤한 사탕
향기로운 커피만 있는 게 아냐
Because it's not all laughing,
happy, candy in the sky...
...coffee at Central Perk.
실제생활이라고, 알아?
성인이라면 그래야 된다고
It's real life, okay?
It's what grownups do.
I think he's right.
맞는 말이야
You guys hang out at
the coffeehouse way too much.
너흰 커피하우스에서
너무 많이 노닥거려
-I feel so guilty about Ross.
-I know.
- 오빠한테 너무 미안하다
- 그러게
I kind of feel like it's my fault.
어째 내 잘못 같다
Kind of?
같아?
You should have kept this to yourself.
너만 입 닫았으면
이런 일 없었잖아
I'm keeping so many things to myself,
something was bound to slip out!
요즘 입 닫을 일이 너무 많아
몇 마디 튀어나왔는갑다
I think it's very brave
what you said.
정말 용감한 발언이었어
I can't sit here anymore.
I have to walk places.
난 그만 나가서
좀 걸어다녀야겠다
What's with the coat?
How about the animal rights thing?
그 코트는 다 뭐야?
동물의 권리는 어떡하고?
이건 내가 책 보고 말하는 건데
밍크는 착한 애들이 아니더라
I've been reading up,
and for your information...
...minks aren't very nice.
-So they deserve to be killed?
-Well, they are real bad.
그럼 죽어도 되나?
걔들 진짜 못돼먹었어
Okay, I admit it.
I love this coat, okay?
좋아, 인정할게
이 코트 맘에 들어
It's the best thing I ever had wrapped
around me, including Phil Huntley.
내 몸을 감싼 것 중 최고야
필 헌틀리도 포함해서
Remember Phil Huntley?
He was fine.
필 헌틀리 기억나?
끝내줬는데
안녕하세요?
So you like the short hair better?
- 짧은 머리가 낫나요?
- 네?
Yeti? Danny?
설인? 대니?
I had to cut my hair to get rid of...
머리를 잘랐어요...
...the fogger smell.
연막탄 냄새 때문에
Listen, I'm so sorry.
I would have never fogged you...
저기, 정말 죄송해요
제가 너무 심했어요
...if you hadn't looked so....
그때는 좀...
- 이해하죠?
- 그럼요
Absolutely. Some people
are just into appearances.
- 외모로만 판단하는 사람도 있죠
- 네?
What?
It's cool.
뭐 괜찮아요
이봐요, 아뇨
괜찮지 않아요
No, that is not cool.
You don't even know me.
날 알지도 못하면서
You got the shopping bags
and the Saks catalog.
왜 이래요, 쇼핑백에
섹스 카탈로그...
이걸로 나란 사람을
다 판단하나요?
From that, you've got me
all figured out?
Well, you don't.
잘못 봤어요
You know, I could have toys
for underprivileged kids in here.
가난한 아이들한테 줄
장난감이 있으면 어쩔래요
Do you?
그래요?
애들이 속옷 갖고 노는 걸
좋아한다면
You know, if kids like to play
with capri pants.
알았어요
Stop saying that.
I hate that!
그거 하지 말아요
듣기 싫으니까
알았어요
좋아요
나도 댁을 판단했어요
I judged you.
I made a snap judgment.
나도 당신을 속단했지만
그쪽은 나보다 더 심했어요
But you did it too, and you're worse.
You're sticking to your judgment.
자기 판단을 과신하고
You can't even open your mind to see
you might be wrong.
그게 잘못된 건지는
생각도 안 해보니까
What does that say about you?
본인은 어떤 사람 같아요?
That pizza place
across the street any good?
- 길 건너 피자집 괜찮나요?
- 뭐요?
I'm hungry.
You want some pizza?
시장한데, 피자 먹을래요?
You can keep yelling.
가서 계속 소리 지릅시다
알았어요
Stop saying that.
I hate that.
하지 말아요
듣기 싫으니까
로스?
Are you still mad?
- 아직 우리한테 화났니?
- 그래
Good! We have an "I'm Sorry" song.
잘됐다
사과의 노래를 준비했거든
You know what?
I'm not in the mood.
지금은 별로 듣고 싶지 않아
저기, 로스...
Look, Ross.
I feel really bad.
You're going through all this stuff...
내가 잘못했어
너 힘든 것도 모르고...
내가 바보처럼 굴었다
...and I just acted like a jerk.
그래, 정말 미안해
-We are so sorry.
-You're stepping on the song.
나 노래 좀 하자
우리가 너무 주제넘었어
We were way out of line, all right?
We totally support you.
우린 네 편이야
어떤 결정을 내리든
오빠를 따를게
Whatever you decide,
whatever you do.
이제 가사까지 훔쳐가니?
Now you're just taking lines
out of the song.
This is hard enough, okay?
I really need you guys right now.
난 지금도 힘들어
너희가 필요하다고
맞아, 바로 그거야
그렇기 때문에...
Yes, exactly! And that's why....
Why don't you come over tonight,
and I'll make your favorite dinner.
오늘 집으로 와
맛있는 저녁 해줄게
좋지?
그래
Thanks, you guys.
고맙다, 얘들아
Are you wearing fur?
피비, 너 모피 입었니?
Let's get some perspective, people.
얘들이 정말 왜 이럴까?
이게 무슨 맹도견 가죽코트니?
It's not like I'm wearing
a seeing-eye dog coat!
You know, I think I kind of
understand why I lost it today.
지금 생각해보니까 오늘
내가 왜 그랬는지 알겠어
You do, huh?
그래?
알다시피...
You see...
...I'm an actor, right?
난 배우잖아, 그치?
So I got to keep my emotions
right at the surface.
늘 감정을 발산해야 돼
처리할 일이 산더미야
무슨 뜻인지 알아?
I got a lot of balls in the air,
you know?
It's tough. Guys like me,
you wander around, you're alone.
참 힘들어, 나 같은 사람은
정처 없는 외로운 나그네...
What are you talking about?
뭔 소릴 하는 거야?
I'm not sure.
나도 모르겠다
얘들아
이게 누구야
어디 갔었어?
Look at you!
Where have you been?
I went to have pizza.
피자 먹고 왔어, 대니랑
With Danny.
-What happened?
-That yeti is one smooth talker.
어쩌다 그렇게 됐는데?
그 설인 말발 끝내주더라
Yetis are smooth-talkers. That's why
you never see any pictures of them.
그래서 걔들 사진이 없는 거야
"Come here, baby. Give me the camera."
'이리 온, 카메라 내놓으시지'
I hope you're not full.
Dinner's almost ready.
배 안 부르지?
저녁 다 됐어
난 그냥 내 방에
있는 게 좋겠다
I think I'll probably
just hang out in my room.
- 안 돼
- 왜 그래?
Why?
내 말 좀 들어봐
Come on, you guys!
If Emily knew I was having dinner
with you, she'd flip out.
너랑 저녁 먹은 걸 에밀리가
알면 어떻게 나올지 알잖아
괜찮아, 난 상관없어
It's okay.
I really don't mind.
Wait, wait. You know what?
Just stay.
잠깐, 그러지 말고 같이 먹자
Please.
부탁이야
It would mean a lot for me
if you stay.
네가 있어주면 좋겠어
Ross, I just
로스, 난...
레이첼, 제발
저녁 같이 먹자
Please, just have dinner with us!
알았어, 조이
진정해라
Settle down.
All right. I'm sorry.
- 괜찮다니까
- 그래, 미안하다
You see, Rach, I'm an actor.
알잖아, 난 배우야
얘들아
Hey, look!
Ugly Naked Guy's back.
저길 봐, 추물단지
알몸사나이가 돌아왔어
세상에, 저 사람
본 게 언제야
We haven't seen him in so long.
Oh, God! I really missed
that fat bastard.
저 뚱땡이 진짜
보고 싶었는데
기분 참 묘하다
This is so weird.
I realized this may be
the last time we hang out together.
이게 우리가 마지막으로
모이는 걸까?
It's almost as if he knew.
저 친구도 알았군
I'll get it.
내가 받을게
여보세요
에밀리?
Hi, Emily.
네, 여기 있어요
잠깐만 기다려요
You tracked him down.
Hold on.
나야
Yeah, we're just having dinner.
그래, 저녁 먹는 중이야
Sure, hold on.
그럼, 잠깐만
인사하겠대
She wants to say hi.
기다려
Hi, Emily!
안녕, 에밀리
Hello, everyone.
다들 반가워요
So who am I saying hello to?
거기 누구누구 있죠?
Well, I don't know
about who's here...
그게...
누가 있는지는 모르지만
레이첼이 없는 건 확실하네
...but I can tell you who's not here,
and that's Rachel!
나도 그러길 바래요
로스도 잘 알 테니까
I should hope not.
Ross knows better than that by now.
You know what?
Rachel is here.
저기, 레이첼도 있어
She's there?
거기 있다고?
아, 저기 있었구나
Oh, yeah, there she is!
She's here.
그래, 함께 있어
Take me off speakerphone.
로스, 수화기 들어봐
됐어
How could you do this to me?
어떻게 이럴 수 있어?
I made my feelings about Rachel
perfectly clear.
레이첼에 대한 내 감정은
확실히 밝혔을 텐데
I'm just having dinner
with my friends, okay?
내 말 좀 들어봐
그냥 친구들이랑
저녁 먹는 거야
-You can't keep away from her.
-That's ridiculous.
레이첼을 멀리할 수
없는 거겠지
말도 안 돼
-Hello? Hello?
-Who is this?
여보세요?
누구쇼?
It's Ross. What are you doing?
로스다, 너 뭐하냐?
Sorry, dude, I had to make a call.
미안하다, 전화 좀 걸려고
Joey.
조이...
Joey, they don't have two lines,
they have two phones.
조이, 라인은 하나야
전화기만 두 개라고
Gotcha.
그렇구나
I'm sorry. Emily, listen.
I have never cheated on you.
미안해, 에밀리
들어봐, 난 자기를
속인 적 없어
자기를 위해 이사도 가고
친구도 버릴 사람이야
I'm moving for you. I'm cutting
friends out of my life for you.
Please, get on the plane
and come to New York, okay?
어서 비행기 타고
뉴욕으로 와
내가 함께 하고픈
사람은 바로 자기야
You're the only one
I want to be with.
I'll feel better when I'm there.
I can know where you are all the time.
나도 가고 싶어
자기가 어딨는지
늘 알 수 있게
그걸 다 알 수는 없어
You can't know where I am
all the time.
This marriage will never work
if you don't trust me.
날 믿지 못하면
이 결혼은 잘될 수 없어
You're right.
맞아
어때... 날 믿을 수 있어?
Can you trust me?
아니
I think it's going okay.
잘되나 보다
Looks like he's smiling.
웃고 있잖아
How can you tell?
You can only see his back.
어떻게 알아?
뒤통수만 보이는데
You can totally tell!
그걸 왜 몰라
Here, look, watch me.
날 잘 보라고
Smile.
웃고, 찡그리고, 웃고
Frown. Smile.
Frown.
찡그리고
Smile.
웃고
I guess that's it.
끝난 것 같다
Why? What happened?
- 왜?
- 어떻게 됐는데?
My marriage is over.
- 이 결혼은 끝이야
- 뭐?
이걸 어째...
Look at you, you're shivering.
어떡해, 떨고 있잖아
Here.
여기
우리가 해줄 건 없을까?
Honey, is there anything we can do?
있어
You can help me
get my furniture back from Gunther.
건터한테 가서 내 가구 찾아오자
알았어, 고문 좀 그만해!
Stop tormenting me!
This is mink, okay? They're mean,
and they hate squirrels.
얘는 밍크야
성질도 포악하고
다람쥐를 싫어해
이 녀석들 대부분은
코트가 되고 싶어하지
Most of these probably
wanted to be coats.
그래, 좋아
알았다고!
Fine. No, I get it.
Here.
여기요
You take it.
가지세요
Are you happy now?
I'm cold!
이제 행복하니?
난 무지 춥다